This time, the Yufeng Battalion
deployed for sea training in the Southeast.
Not only did they successfully complete
various sea-crossing and island-landing
offensive and defensive drills,
but they also coordinated with academies
and military production units
to complete their respective tasks.
Excellent work.
However,
what is even more commendable
is that they assisted local police
in jointly taking down
a high-tech
drug trafficking syndicate,
and successfully rescued the hostages.
Highly commendable.
Brigade Commander Xu,
you left out one hero.
Yes.
The heroes of this operation,
apart from the troops of Yufeng Battalion,
also include our Red First Battalion's
former recon squad leader,
Comrade Wu Dongsheng.
The Ministry of Veterans Affairs issued a document
commending Comrade Wu Dongsheng's heroic deeds.
Excellent.
The higher authorities,
regarding your operation this time,
are extremely satisfied.
The People's Army will always be the protector of the people.
The Commissar and I discussed it,
and we're giving you two days off.
Get some good rest.
Relax a bit.
Get some sleep.
Stand up!
Thank you, Chief!
Salute!
Aren't we being a bit too lax?
We should still maintain our combat readiness, right?
I know what you're worried about.
But the Brigade Commander himself said
to give the Yufeng Battalion two days off.
We have to let everyone get some rest.
If they're always this tense,
they're going to snap eventually.
Besides, I've replaced tonight's sentries
with our core personnel.
Security hasn't loosened up,
and our combat readiness measures are still in place.
So there shouldn't be any issues.
You go back and get some rest.
I'll go check on the motor pool.
Alright. If anything happens,
let me know immediately.
Okay.
Honey,
the commander gave us two days off starting tomorrow.
I want to wake up early
and hurry to the supermarket
to make a nice meal for you guys.
So, um,
could you send me a WeChat red packet
for a hundred first?
Great, thanks, honey!
That goose stew I made last time,
do you want to have it again?
Then could you make that red packet
two hundred instead?
Awesome, thanks, honey!
Alright.
You hang up first.
I'm going to sleep soon too.
Bye.
You're on duty.
Stop yawning.
Platoon Leader, you have to trust science.
Scientifically speaking,
yawning can't be controlled.
Besides,
it's our own camp.
See?
Look sharp.
Keep an eye on things here.
I'm going to go check over there.
Don't worry, Platoon Leader.
Keep your eyes peeled.
Xiaoshan,
What's up?
Brother,
I've resolved Wu Dongsheng's issue
once and for all.
What do you mean "once and for all"?
What did you do to him?
I sorted out his love life.
How's that for "once and for all"?
Chen Xiaoshan, stop messing around.
Don't just casually
set him up with unreliable girls.
Then do you think I
am reliable?
You're even more unreliable.
Wait,
what's that supposed to mean?
Don't let one heroic rescue
confuse your feelings for him.
Do you even know the difference
between gratitude and love?
I'm a grown woman now.
You think I can't tell the difference?
Then all my past relationships
would've been for nothing.
I'm just afraid it's a passing phase for you,
and later you'll suddenly lose interest,
and just walk away.
Then what about Wu Dongsheng?
Brother,
get your facts straight.
I'm your sister.
Shouldn't you be worried about me getting hurt?
I know what kind of man Wu Dongsheng is.
He's loyal to his career,
and he's the same with people.
Once he falls for you,
he'll treat you well with all his heart.
Even if
it means sacrificing himself,
he would never hurt anyone.
Brother,
as you know,
everything you just said
is exactly why I love him.
A good man like him
in this day and age
is incredibly rare.
Of course, I won't let anyone else steal him away.
I have to hold on to him tightly.
Silly girl.
If you're really determined to win him over,
you need to take it steady.
Please, I'm Chen Xiaoshan.
You can rest easy.
I have everything under control.
Let me tell you,
with the way you are,
he might not even be into you.
Stop right there.
Just figure out whose side you're on,
and we'll be fine.
Alright,
I'm done talking to you.
Looks like Wu Dongsheng is becoming my brother-in-law.
What's going on?
The helicopters outside are so loud.
How is anyone supposed to sleep?
Who are you?
Don't move!
Mountain Eagle.
This is Honey Badger.
I'm in the woods to the right behind the building.
Awaiting orders.
Immediately contact the independently garrisoned
long-range artillery and army aviation detachments.
Be ready to counterattack at any time.
Copy that.
Comrades of Yufeng Battalion,
I have good news for you.
At 1:04 a.m. Beijing Time,
you
gloriously became POWs of Jufeng Battalion.
Report!
Battalion Commander Jiang,
you're playing dirty!
What kind of hero uses a sneak attack?
Sneak attacks
are your Battalion Commander Guo's specialty.
I'm just using his own tricks.
Giving him a taste
of his own medicine.
It was you who let your guard down,
which gave us the opportunity.
Report!
we haven't found Guo Zijian.
Guo Zijian,
I know you're nearby.
Come out.
Face this fair and square, like a man.
Face your own defeat,
and stand with your comrades.
Share the blessings,
and share the burdens.
Slipping away by yourself
is not the style of a commander.
Mountain Eagle,
Honey Badger here. I can't reach anyone.
Honey Badger,
prepare for the next plan.
Move out.
Copy that.
Guo Zijian,
don't waste your effort.
You should understand
that my standing here
means all your combat nodes
have been taken down by me.
I know you still have support fire,
but your comrades are here.
Do you dare to open fire?
Comrades of Yufeng Battalion,
do you see this?
This is your battalion commander.
He abandoned you,
watched helplessly as you became prisoners,
and then, all by himself,
slunk away in disgrace.
Jiang Shengqiang!
Jiang Shengqiang,
If I had a gun right now,
you wouldn't be talking so much nonsense.
Battalion Commander Guo.
Long time no see.
Did you miss me?
You've lost your mind trying to win.
Got nothing better to do this late at night?
Don't take it out on me.
You should think about it.
Would I dare to come to the 396th Brigade's camp
and make such a big scene
without orders from above?
Would I just ask for trouble?
The brigade commander personally said
our Yufeng Battalion gets a two-day leave.
But another commander also personally said
that your Yufeng Battalion
must maintain at least Level 3 combat readiness.
And he specifically emphasized that
without his personal permission,
it cannot be lifted.
Did you forget?
Regarding this operation of Yufeng Battalion,
both the corps and brigade
commanders take it very seriously.
They hope you will exercise
your own initiative,
and no matter what,
fight this battle well.
Yes, sir.
Also, there's one requirement
I must emphasize.
Deputy Corps Commander Liang directed
that Yufeng Battalion, from this day forward,
must maintain at least Level 3 combat readiness
until returning to camp.
And only upon receiving his personal orders
can it be lifted.
Battalion Commander Guo,
I'd like to ask,
if not for that
flawless joint military and police operation,
if not for the post-victory
superiors,
society,
and the media's universal acclaim,
and more importantly,
if the brigade commander
hadn't personally promised a two-day leave,
would you, Guo Zijian,
have allowed your constant state of combat readiness
to suddenly slip tonight?
I know
you still have Yang Maolin pulling the strings.
I also know
you still have some fire strike capabilities
that can turn the camp into a sea of fire.
But your command post is here.
Your comrades are here.
And you yourself
are here too.
Guo Zijian,
you've lost.
Don't you dare tell me about starting over.
Why should I give you a chance to start over?
Just one squad machine gun
can wipe out your entire unit.
What chance do you have to start over?
Jiang Shengqiang.
Cut the chatter.
Attention!
Commander,
the exercise has been successfully completed.
Awaiting your orders!
At ease!
Yes, sir!
Truly an eye-opener.
At ease.
Before me
stands such a Yufeng Battalion.
I know deep down,
some of you are definitely unconvinced.
Some of you keep wondering
what Liang Beihua is going to say
to make our lives miserable.
I didn't have to say certain things,
but facing
such a Yufeng Battalion today,
I have to say a few words.
So prick up your ears and listen closely.
Throughout history,
war
has never been about normal conditions,
nor is it about social pleasantries.
Once you put on that uniform,
you are soldiers.
There is no high or low status.
But in war,
someone must step up first.
If an emergency arises,
do you comfortably sit back
and wait for your number to be called,
or wait for a rotation?
Tell me, can you?
No! No! No!
You know you can't.
I remember before
leaving for this sea training,
I issued an order.
The Yufeng Battalion
must always maintain Level 3 combat readiness or higher.
And this order
could only be
lifted by me.
But,
after the brigade leaders
suggested giving you time off,
the commander of the Yufeng Battalion
compromised it.
For the combat readiness sentries that should've been set,
not a single detachment was assigned.
Why?
Because your Guo Zijian,
Commander Guo,
loves his soldiers.
But by doing so,
he also harmed his soldiers.
This operation
was an exercise the group army
had long prepared for you.
Originally, the Jufeng Battalion
was ready to fight a fierce battle against you.
But now,
it's totally one-sided.
It's turned into a game of herding pigs.
The chiefs are all very disappointed.
Jufeng Battalion on the perimeter,
are you secretly gloating?
Take a good look for yourselves.
How many of you
have been secretly marked
and turned into potential targets?
Report!
Commander!
I want to say,
no matter how capable Yang Maolin is,
on his own,
what can he possibly change?
I'm not discussing what he can change.
Go back
and use your heads
to reflect on this carefully.
Yes, sir!
I now announce
that starting from now,
Yufeng Battalion
will stand down.
You have two days of leave.
Yes, sir!
Attention!
Jufeng Battalion!
Return to quarters!
Right face! Double time, march!
Yufeng Battalion!
Here, sir!
Listen to my orders.
Everyone,
regardless of gender,
regardless of branch,
regardless of specialty,
regardless of position,
in five minutes,
assemble at the physical training ground by unit!
Everyone
will do a ten-kilometer armed cross-country run!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Staying up in the middle of the night.
Looks like this kid
got worked up.
The Yufeng Battalion has been too proud lately.
If they don't vent this frustration,
who can sleep?
Instead of tossing and turning,
it's better to open an outlet
and let this frustration
out.
The Commissar is right.
This is the true art of commanding troops.
A few requirements.
First,
when running late at night,
no loud noises!
Second,
if you can't keep up, drop out immediately!
Third,
after the training is over,
no need to fall in.
Squad leaders will count heads and take you back.
And then,
take a shower and sleep!
Tomorrow is a day off!
Double time, march!
He knows when to take charge and when to let go.
He knows when to loosen up and when to rein in.
This kid
has matured a lot.
Knowing how to balance tension and relaxation
is the way to adjust body and mind.
Based on the current situation,
by tomorrow afternoon at the latest,
the entire exercise will be completely over.
This Black Mamba 404th Brigade
is a bit arrogant.
They claimed their combat resources
haven't even been depleted by half,
and they haven't fought enough.
But he didn't expect
that his words
would be captured by the monitoring system.
However, some speculate
that Long Yuanshan
said this on purpose for the directorate to hear.
They do have the capability.
But,
the group army commanders are losing face.
Because organizing the 399th Brigade
and the 404th Brigade in this live-combat confrontation
involves Commander Huang
and Professor Zhang from the National Defense University
jointly promoting a new subject.
I know about this.
Military reform
always requires trials and exploration.
That is why
in this confrontation,
not only have the Theater Army commanders and headquarters
come to observe,
but some related academies
have also specifically sent experts to the exercise site.
I heard that in the directorate,
not only is there a gathering of generals,
but the professors' shoulder boards
are also shining with stars.
What exactly are you trying to say?
If right now,
you can find the right moment
to roll out the Yufeng Battalion's
Value Cube,
then it would completely be
Commander Huang and Professor Zhang setting the stage,
and you putting on the show.
Commander Huang sent you to put on this act, didn't he?
It was
the Chief of Staff.
It's all the same.
The Chief said,
saving the show is as urgent as fighting a fire.
Do you really think this is a show?
The Yufeng Battalion just got back from the southeast coast.
They were pushed hard all night,
and have only rested for a day.
These two days of leave
are very precious to them.
You should at least let these young folks
see their partners or something.
The Chief is aware of the situation,
but at this time,
it wouldn't be appropriate for anyone else to step in.
Besides,
last time,
Yufeng Battalion's urban combat drill with the 404th Brigade
didn't go very well.
If at this time,
they can showcase the results of their field training
on the southeast coast,
it would also help rebuild their confidence.
All right.
Your show is over.
Go back and report.
Yes, sir.
We just got back,
and haven't even settled in yet.
Why must we get involved in this fuss?
For no other reason
than to test the Yufeng Battalion's training results.
Guo Zijian
is no match for Long Yuanshan anyway.
I'm just afraid he'll end up embarrassing himself.
He was a defeated opponent in the past.
But now,
not necessarily.
Impossible.
In the past,
I would've said it's impossible too.
But now,
this wishful thinking of it being 'impossible'
could very well turn into a slap in our own faces.
I admit,
my attitude towards Guo Zijian
was indeed a bit extreme in the past.
Actually, as a person,
he has no selfish motives,
and he dares to take responsibility.
This is something
neither you nor I might be able to do.
How can he compare to you?
Anyway, regarding him,
I still reserve my personal opinion.
In this confrontation,
the 399th Brigade not only brought out all they had,
but was also assigned the Theater Army's
combat support brigade,
and cutting-edge weapons from the intel brigade.
A truly formidable lineup.
But in this battle,
they performed absolutely dismally.
If I remember correctly,
the 399th
is a recent
pilot unit for the Theater Army's systemic warfare.
Last time,
during the systemic warfare demo at Yunlin Mountain,
they left a deep impression.
I remember you, Professor Zhang,
used four keywords to evaluate them:
Vertically and horizontally linked,
Integrated recon and strike,
Flawless.
Yes.
For so many years,
recon, early warning, and perception were hard;
fusing and sharing situational awareness was hard;
command and control linkage was hard;
information network protection was hard;
and precise support implementation was hard.
This was hard, that was hard.
Ultimately, realizing systemic warfare was hard.
The 399th Brigade used high-level system integration
to successfully solve this series of problems.
It was thrilling.
Lao Huang.
But this time,
it was the key to their success,
but also the cause of their defeat.
Exactly.
I think their system integration
only achieved a basic level of connectivity.
But everyone praised it so highly,
that it confused even them.
The 404th Brigade
knew they had the upper hand in this area,
so they must have made targeted preparations.
So it's not surprising the battle turned out like this.
That's because they ran into Long Yuanshan.
With a different opponent, it's hard to say.
If war allowed us to choose our opponents,
we could always find a winning countermeasure.
Lao Liang,
what are you thinking about?
I'm thinking the 399th Brigade
still has a reserve unit they can use.
On the invisible information battlefield,
as for this reserve unit,
I wonder what tactical tricks
they can pull off.
You have to use your best assets where it counts.
Let's wait and see.
Staff Officer Liang,
this is your 3D information platform's
first battle since its establishment.
How about we use
Long Yuanshan's 404th Brigade
to draw first blood?
No problem.
I've been pondering since we got the mission.
If we want to take on the 404th Brigade,
our old tricks won't work.
We must use something new
for it to be effective.
That's right.
Long Yuanshan knows us far too well.
As soon as we make a move, he'll know it's us.
To be honest,
even while staying mobile with the troops,
my mind hasn't been idle.
I considered several battle plans,
but I think the most suitable one
is Operation Diana.
Operation Diana?
Received orders from above.
Sync frequencies with the 396th Brigade's Yufeng Battalion ASAP.
Sync with them?
We've done our fighting,
and now they step in?
We can only blame our poor performance earlier.
I've long heard how incredible Guo Zijian is.
Let's see what he's made of this time.
We're all pilot units.
Let's see what weapons and tricks they're hiding.
It's a good learning opportunity.
Don't be so narrow-minded.
Yes, sir.
The group army sent them as our reserve force.
They must have their reasons.
Now let's see between Long Yuanshan and Guo Zijian,
who adapts faster.
Brigade Commander,
do you think
we should slow down the pace?
To save some face for the 399th Brigade,
and leave a good impression on the observation group?
Why complicate things?
Although the 399th Brigade suffered heavy losses,
its command center
remains completely intact.
And it hasn't been discovered yet.
As long as the brain still exists,
we can't let our guard down.
Without limbs,
what's the use of a good brain?
Tiejun,
I think these recent victories have made you complacent.
The exercise isn't over yet.
It's hard to say who will win.
It's like playing chess.
Even if you have all your major pieces,
but they're out of position,
while the opponent only has a knight and a pawn,
if they are perfectly positioned,
they can still turn the tables.
You mean a crossed pawn acting as a rook.
In future warfare, with almost complete firepower
and long-range strike capabilities,
a small detachment,
if backed by a complete info support system,
only needs to provide a few key strike targets
to completely destroy
a powerful army.
If it were our assault detachment,
I believe we could achieve that effect.
As for the 399th Brigade...
Unlikely.
Report!
Successfully synced with the 399th Brigade's frequency.
Connection established.
Get Commander Wang on the line.
Yes, sir.
01, go ahead. 01, go ahead.
01, copy. 01, copy.
Commander Wang, this is Guo Zijian.
Battalion Commander Guo, hello.
You've seen the situation.
The Red Force's situation is not optimistic right now.
What's your plan?
Commander Wang,
per Exercise Control's orders,
from now on,
please have your comms and electronic warfare units
rapidly share all your info equipment frequencies,
functions, and deployments,
along with their current locations,
to me as soon as possible.
During this time,
I need you to maintain full electronic silence,
including contact with remaining combat forces.
Understood. I'll follow your lead.
Commander Huang,
is this what you called
the prime steel reserved for the blade's edge?
A reinforced battalion
won't even make Long Yuanshan break a sweat.
The positioning of the Red Army's reserve
is actually a stroke of genius.
It doesn't seem like their style at all.
This 399th Brigade is quite bold.
We crippled one unit, and another one shows up.
The pawn that crossed the river has appeared.
Send an assault squad to track it closely right away.
Once the target is spotted,
suppress it with close, medium, and long-range firepower.
I want to see how this pawn that crossed the river
plans to face my chariots, horses, and cannons.
Yes, sir. I'll arrange it immediately.
Orders.
Combat Team One,
advance to Hill 209 north of Tiger's Mouth.
Although this area is occupied by the Blue Army,
our goal is to pull teeth right from the tiger's mouth.
The key to this battle is the element of surprise.
Stay concealed.
Yes, sir.
Combat Team Two,
move along the southern section of Liuzhuang by Shigun River
and the western section of Fangzhuang to approach the enemy covertly.
The focus of this battle is on Tiger's Mouth
and the Blue Army stationed at Jade Emperor Peak.
Hit them with heavy firepower.
The drone detachment will send a squad
to provide you with intelligence.
Yes, sir.
Combat Team Three will act as the reserve,
stationed at Liuligou
and the Ermashan area to the south.
Yes, sir.
Since the mission is highly dynamic,
Air Assault, Long-Range Artillery,
Comms, Electronic Warfare,
and the Special Ops Platoon
must maintain communications with me at all times.
Yes, sir.
The reserve unit's position is well-chosen.
Too bad he's up against Long Yuanshan.
Platoon Leader!
All units are on the move.
What are we waiting for?
What's the rush?
Platoon Leader!
The Battalion Commander is here.
Salute!
Commander, what brings you here in person?
Need you ask? Our mission is critical.
You're catching on, kid.
Commander, if I couldn't figure that out,
I shouldn't be the squad leader.
Not bad. Keep it up.
Your mission this time is very simple,
but very important.
We need to establish a
real yet virtual communications command station.
Although the equipment is simulated,
the simulation requirements are high.
It requires Communications and ECM,
executed jointly by two three-man teams.
The tactics we researched on the southeast coast this time...
whether they are viable and effective...
This operation
is the best opportunity to test them.
Are you confident?
Yes!
Good.
Confidence comes from strong capabilities and competence.
Our Yufeng Battalion
has never conceded defeat on the battlefield.
Staff Liang,
I have confidence in our strength.
I believe in you all.
For this operation,
the Special Ops Platoon will go with you.
They are responsible for protection,
while you are responsible for searching for targets,
and
completing the key tasks together.
Understood?
Understood!
Commander,
bringing a few little girls along...
how do we fight this battle?
What do you mean by 'little girls'?
They're our battalion's precious assets.
Let me tell you,
the core of your mission this time
is to ensure their safety.
Understood!
Mission accomplishment guaranteed!
The helicopters can't take you too far.
You'd be easily detected.
So for the rest of the way,
you'll have to rely on your own two feet.
No matter what methods you use,
you must keep these precious assets
well protected for me.
Yes, sir!
If you encounter an insurmountable obstacle,
sacrifice yourselves
to save your comrades.
Sacrifice ourselves?
Without us Special Forces, how do we fight this battle?
Remember our Value Cube?
The 'little girls' you mentioned
are exactly
the core of the cube for this mission.
Report.
Go ahead.
We just intercepted
the Red Army reserve's
communication frequency with the Red Army command post,
but it was too brief to track.
There's just one strange thing.
Get to the point.
All of the Red Army's communications have been cut off.
They've gone radio silent.
Yes, sir.
Monitor them closely.
Radio silence means one of three things.
First, they fear our heavy electromagnetic jamming.
Second, they fear being tracked down by us.
Third,
there are new deployments
for their combat troops and command elements.
It's obviously the third one.
And to coordinate with this reserve force,
the entire Red Army's communication and command system
is providing full support.
It's highly likely that this reserve force
is preparing a fatal strike.
We've reached this stage of the battle,
what kind of fatal strike could they have left?
Order the assault squad
to expand their search area.
I don't believe
a combined arms battalion
can hide its tracks from me.
I'll deploy them immediately.
Report.
Captain.
These two
are assault members from the 399th Brigade.
They were scattered,
but managed to survive.
That's great.
Which battalion of the 399th Brigade are you from?
Sir!
We're from the 9th Company, 3rd Combined Arms Battalion.
I know, I know.
Your 9th Company Commander, Xu Zhiqiang...
We know each other very well.
We attended training together.
Even shared the same dorm.
How is he doing now?
Don't tell me he was eliminated too.
Our Commander Xu
had escaped with two infantry fighting vehicles,
but was spotted by the enemy's assault squad.
He didn't make it in the end.
That's a shame.
Where are they now?
Just over that hill ahead.
Is there any surviving equipment left?
There's one infantry fighting vehicle
and one assault gun vehicle,
along with over 20 comrades.
Good.
Excellent.
Go contact them immediately.
We'll head over shortly.
Yes, sir.
Assemble the troops.
We depart immediately.
Yes, sir.
You two be careful on the way.
Get two men to tail them.
Yes, sir.
How did you encounter them?
They were discovered by our scouts.
I've already checked.
What they're wearing
and their insignias are indeed from the 399th Brigade.
But when you questioned them just now,
they gave themselves away.
The 399th Brigade suffered heavy losses this time.
A large portion of their heavy equipment
was destroyed by small squads like this.
They rely on their familiarity with the terrain.
Small in number and highly mobile,
they're very hard to deal with.
Then why did you let them go?
I was just wondering
how to attract
Long Yuanshan's attention,
and he delivered himself right to our door.
What should we do about the company
that appeared near Tiger's Mouth?
Judging from the intel brought back by the scouts,
it is indeed a reinforced company.
Staff Officer Liu!
Sir!
Order the Recon Battalion
to immediately search the area around Tiger's Mouth.
Yes, sir!
Tiger's Mouth, as a Red Army position,
is now of absolutely no value.
What is this reinforced company doing there?
There are two possibilities.
First,
the 1st and 2nd Battalions didn't clear the battlefield thoroughly,
and there are still personnel and equipment left behind.
Second,
Tiger's Mouth is the central area of the exercise field.
No matter which direction they strike from,
it would be highly advantageous.
I'll immediately order the 1st and 2nd Battalions
to expand their search area.
If spotted, annihilate them on the spot.
Is this really the killer move they came up with?
Trying to turn the tide with just one reinforced company?
They severely underestimate me, Long Yuanshan.
Although the Red Army reserves went into total radio silence,
they have neither tactics nor a sound strategy.
They're just delaying the inevitable.
Platoon Leader Yang, we have a situation.
Stay alert.
I finally caught you.
Comrades.
Team One, pinpoint the location.
Team Two, capture the frequency.
Ma Zhengzheng.
Here.
Night vision binoculars.
Staff Officer Liang.
Here!
Is my plan too risky?
Not really.
There's no problem with the plan itself.
If it were a couple of years ago,
it would've been highly unlikely.
But the technology is much more mature now,
and partially implemented.
So it's good to put it into practice.
If this battle is a success,
the commanders might ask you for the underlying principles.
What will you say?
Reporting to the commanders,
isn't that your job?
That won't do.
This is your show this time.
I don't care about that.
Then what do you care about?
What I care about is,
Hong Xiafei and Yang Maolin have been out for a while.
Shouldn't they have sent some intel back by now?
Reporting, Squad Leader!
Coordinates accurate. Image capture complete.
Good job.
I'll send the parameters to the command post right away.
Wait a minute.
We can't wait any longer.
We're running out of time.
Something's not right.
This command post is likely a fake, too.
That's impossible.
Knowing Brigade Commander Long,
he would never
set up a command post so conspicuously
that we could easily spot it with night vision.
Platoon Leader.
At a time like this,
you can't keep...
Cut the crap.
If that's really the case,
then we're doomed.
We'd rather be late,
but we must be accurate.
This is our special ops platoon's
core principle for intelligence operations.
Also,
if we provide a false target,
then all decisions made by the command post
will be built on an illusion.
So what do we do?
Judging from how busy the female soldiers were,
this should be an intelligence processing station,
deliberately disguised as a command post.
Besides,
the guards are positioned perfectly.
My guess is
the real command post isn't far from here.
No more than two kilometers at most.
Are you sure?
About eighty percent sure.
Let's cut the chatter.
Let's move out.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I think I sprained my ankle.